<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">NJ GSET Guide</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search</string>
    <string name="explore_msg">Explore Rutgers..</string>
    <string name="title_activity_descriptions">Descriptions</string>
    <string-array name="locations_array">
        <item>BEST_West_Residence_Hall</item>
        <item>Science_and_Engineering_Research_Center</item>
        <item>Busch_Dining_Hall</item>
        <item>Busch_Campus_Center</item>
        <item>Biomedical_Engineering_Building</item>
        <item>Center_for_Advanced_Infrastructure_and_Transporation</item>
        <item>Computing_Research_and_Education_Building</item>
        <item>Engineering_Building</item>
        <item>Fiber_Optic_Materials_Research_Building</item>
        <item>Protips</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="BEST_West_Residence_Hall_desc">
        The Busch Engineering, Science, and Technology West Residence Hall, commonly referred to as just "BEST", will become your 
        home away from home for the next four weeks. The rooms are obscenely luxurious and spacious for college dorms as the 
        building was constructed recently in 2011. Each room houses two scholars and is connected by a bathroom to an adjacent 
        room. This room-bathroom-room structure is called a suite. Make sure to get along well with your roommate and suitemates
        because you will work on various projects, such as robotics, together as a two or four person group. Of course you should 
        make friends with everyone at GSET, not just your suitemates!   
    </string>
	<string name="Science_and_Engineering_Research_Center_desc">
	    Abbreviated as SERC (pron. S-ER-K), this building will be where the GSET orientation is held for both parents and
	    scholars. During the orientation, you will meet the hardworking individuals behind GSET, including but not limited to
	    Dean Rosen, Dean Antoine, and your gorgeous RTAs. When not serving as an orientation center, SERC is the location of 
	    math and computer science courses. Make sure not to talk in the halls as summer courses are ongoing. 
	    Perhaps most importantly, this building is a haven for all those that love to live in subzero temperatures. The air 
	    conditioning here is turned on to max 24/7. This will be your biggest blessing after walking in the Piscatway heat all
	    the way from BEST (approx. 10000 miles) to attend classes.    
	</string>
	<string name="Busch_Dining_Hall_desc">
	    The Busch Dining Hall will be where you eat for the majority of your meals (except catered meals, which are held at BEST).
	    Make sure to have your meal card ready when you get to the doors. 
	    
	    For breakfast, there are scrambled eggs with a choice of protein (often sausage or bacon), and a side of potatoes 
	    (often in the form of hash browns or tater tots). You can accompany your breakfast with a lovely side of fresh fruits
	    from the fruit bar, or if you are feeling particularly peckish, indulge in an unlimited supply of donuts.
	    
	    For lunch,   
	</string>
	<string name="Busch_Campus_Center_desc">
	    There are no classes held in the campus center; however savvy RTAs will lead their groups through this air conditioned 
	    building in order to avoid the heat. 
	</string>
	<string name="Biomedical_Engineering_Building_desc"></string>
	<string name="Center_for_Advanced_Infrastructure_and_Transportation_desc">
	    Abbreviated as CAIT (pron. K-AY-T), this building is the center for civil engineering. Occasionally, keynote speakers
	    will present here. If you do take an architecture course, it will most likely take place in CAIT. 
	</string>
	<string name="Computing_Research_and_Education_Building_desc">
	    Shortened to CoRE (pron. K-OR), the Computing Research and Education Building is the main building for computer 
	    science. Currently, no classes are held in this building, but computer programming research project groups often meet
	    their mentors here.
	</string>
	<string name="Engineering_Building_desc">
	    Several classes and projects take place in the Engineering Building. The bountiful laboratories and tools available
	    in this building make it a catch-all for various research projects and classes. If you are in a pharmacy, chemistry, or
	    materials engineering class, expect to spend at least 6 hours here each week. 
	</string>
	<string name="Protips_desc">
        of your meal card, BEST key card, and room key 
	</string>
	
	<string name="BEST_West_Residence_Hall_addr">
	    54 Bevier Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854
	</string>
	<string name="Science_and_Engineering_Research_Center_addr">
	    118 Frelinghuysen Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8019
	</string>
	<string name="Busch_Dining_Hall_addr">
	    608 Bartholomew Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8002
	</string>
	<string name="Busch_Campus_Center_addr">
	    604 Bartholomew Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8002
	</string>
	<string name="Biomedical_Engineering_Building_addr">
	    599 Taylor Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-5610
	</string>
	<string name="Center_for_Advanced_Infrastructure_and_Transportation_addr">
	    100 Brett Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8058
	</string>
	<string name="Computing_Research_and_Education_Building_addr">
	    96 Frelinghuysen Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8018
	</string>
	<string name="School_of_Engineering_Building_addr">
	    98 Brett Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8058
	</string>
	<string name="Fiber_Optic_Materials_Research_Building_addr">
	    101 Bevier Road
		Piscataway, NJ 08854-8007
	</string>
	<string name="Protips_addr">
	    101 School of Hard Knocks
	    Life, The World 
	</string>
</resources>
